(Bernadette:)We decided to go down to city hall
this afternoon, get married...
(Bernadette:)...and then have the reception
when Howard gets back.
- That's so great.
- Cool.
(Howard:)We know it's short notice,
but we'd love you all to come with us.
(Amy:)No, no, no,
this is not the wedding I wanted.
l wanna wear
my maid-of-honor dress...
(Amy:)...walk down the aisle
with a hundred eyes on me...
(Amy:)...while a string quartet plays
"The way You Look Tonight."
That wasn't our processional music.
Well, it was gonna be mine.
(Sheldon:)Thank you for the invitation,
but I have to decline...
(Sheldon:)...because it doesn't sound like
something I'll enjoy.
Come on, it'll be fun.
(Sheldon:)That's what you said about
the Green Lantern movie.
(Sheldon:)You were 114 minutes of wrong.
(Bernadette:)So, what do you say, Amy?
- Can I wear my maid-of-honor dress?
- Seriously? Wear that thing to city hall?
(Amy:)It's all I have left.
You gonna take that from me too?